Muhsin Hameed



normanbellenger@protonmail.com



linkedin.com/in/muhsin-h



+2349098661465



https://muhsin-h.herokuapp.com/

Summary

I have 5+ years experience working with Python. I am very passionate about data and learning by developing

I have built personal projects that involved web-scraping, data cleaning, data analysis, data visualizations and some Machine learning approaches.

Finally I built and launched Wizemart; a Flask website that uses Google cloud platform to help users find good deals from the best sellers on jumia. I am always looking for a challenge to learn new things and improve.

Experience



Data Scientist

Sep 2021 - Present (5 months +)



Student Intern

Baze University

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020 (3 months)

Analyzed school's hospital plans in order to find optimum locations where sockets and internet ports should be set up.

Analyzed the schools security camera set up.

Developed SQL database schema in a group with other interns Organized/attended weekly meetings to analyze all interns progress

Troubleshooting computers in school's labs

Education



Baze University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2018 - 2021

Licenses & Certifications



What is Data Science? - Coursera



Tools for Data Science - Coursera

3X5F363B7ARG



Data Science Methodology - Coursera

NCG287P2E4GT



Python for Data Science, Al & Development - Coursera

T69VY7FKC9HQ



Database Design and Programming with SQL - Oracle

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • Full-Stack Development • Tableau • Git • Flask • IT Consulting • Jupyter • Data Science • Statistics • Java